Preliminary Guide to the Treasurers Office records, 1903-1990 RG0008
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Treasurers Office records
1903-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0008
72.5 Linear Feet
The Executive Vice President and Treasurer writes the yearly budget report for the Board of Trustees. The material in this collection includes brochures, forms, ledger books, microfilm, budget reports, scrapbooks, awards, estate and gift files, financial records, financial reports, president's reports, framed photographs, and memorabilia.
Restrictions on Access
Series 2,3,4,6,7,11,13,14 and 15 are closed to research for 50 years from date of record creation..
Acquisition Information
Acquisition information is unknown.
Historical note
The Executive Vice President and Treasurer writes the yearly budget report for the Board of Trustees.
Scope and Contents
The material in this collection includes brochures, forms, ledger books, microfilm, budget reports, scrapbooks, awards, estate and gift files, financial records, financial reports, president's reports, framed photographs, and memorabilia. These records date from 1903 to 2010. Not all of the series are processed. Please see staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into eighteen series: Brochures, Financial records, Financial records, Financial records, Awards, Estate records, Financial records, Scrapbooks, Office files, Office files, Financial records, Financial records, three titled Sponsored Research projects, Office files, Certificates, and Reports, photographs, and memorabilia.
Scrapbooks; Washington (D.C.); Budget; Finance; George Washington University
- Brochures, 1969; RG0008 Series 1; .25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains brochures and forms from the cashiers office. They are from 1969.
  Formerly vertical files.
  - Cashier's Office, circa 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Financial records, 1903-1982; RG0008 Series 2; 2.5 Linear feet
  This series contains Treasurer's statements, general cash books, trust fund cash books, student receipt books, and a ledger. The material covers the dates 1903-1982.
  Formerly ACC#5.
  - Treasurer's Monthly Statements, 1903-1910 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trial Balance Book, 1916-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Security and Trust Company Account Book, 1908-1912 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Trust Funds Journal, 1912-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gift Record, 1927-1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General Cash Books, 1918-1947; 4 Linear Feet 4 cash books
    General note
    4 volumes
    - General Cash Book Vol. 1, April, 1918 - January, 1922; This book contains a ledger of payments recieved by the college, month by month for various expenses. This includes tuition, room, board, thesis binding, rentals, and other miscellaneous fees, along with a running total of the payment amounts. Volume 1/4.; Large pale green ledger with red leather binding, corners, and title. Deteriorating leather gives off redrot residue. Binding, espcially the spine, is extremely fragile. Handle with care. Measures 16.5" x 15.5". (Volume 1-4, Volume 1)
    - General Cash Book Vol. 2, February, 1922 - November, 1927; This book contains a ledger of payments recieved by the college, month by month for various expenses. This includes tuition, room, board, thesis binding, rentals, and other miscellaneous fees, along with a running total of the payment amounts. Volume 2/4.; Large pale green ledger with red leather binding, corners, and title. Deteriorating leather gives off redrot residue. Binding, espcially the spine, is fragile. Handle with care. Measures 16.5" x 15.5". (Volume 1-4, Volume 2)
    - General Cash Book Vol. 3, December, 1927 - August, 1929; This book contains a ledger of payments recieved by the college, month by month for various expenses. This includes tuition, room, board, thesis binding, rentals, and other miscellaneous fees, along with a running total of the payment amounts. Volume 3/4.; Large pale green ledger with red leather binding, corners, and title. Title on cover reads "General Cash Book |B| The George Washington University." Deteriorating leather gives off redrot residue. Binding, espcially the spine, is extremely fragile. Handle with care. Measures 16.5" x 15.5". (Volume 1-4, Volume 3)
    - General Cash Book Vol. 4, September, 1941 - December, 1947; This book contains a ledger of payments recieved by the college, month by month for various expenses. This includes tuition, room, board, thesis binding, rentals, and other miscellaneous fees, along with a running total of the payment amounts. Volume 4/4.; Large pale green ledger with red leather binding, corners, and title. Deteriorating leather gives off redrot residue. Binding, espcially the spine, is extremely fragile. Handle with care. Measures 16.5" x 15.5". (Volume 1-4, Volume 4)
  - Charge Journal, March, 1937 - January, 1946; Large pale green ledger with red leather binding, corners, and title. Deteriorating leather gives off redrot residue. Binding, espcially the spine, is fragile. Handle with care. Measures 16.5" x 19". (Volume 1)
    1 volume
  - Voucher Register, March, 1922 - March, 1923 (Volume 1)
  - Trust Funds Cash Books, 1945-1966
    3 volumes
    - Trust Funds Cash Book Vol. 1, September, 1945 - July, 1951; This book contains the payments and reciepts related to GWU accounts on stocks, bonds, scholarship funds, and other funds from September 1, 1945 to July 31, 1951.; Large pale green ledger book (16" x 14.5"). Cover reads "Trust Funds Cash Book The George Washington University | Sept. 1, 1945 - July 31, 1951. Good Condition. (Volume 1-3: RG0008, Series 2, Volume 1)
    - Trust Funds Cash Receipts Vol. 2, April, 1963 - January, 1965; This book includes reciepts for cash payments recieved by the University from April 29, 1963 - January 17, 1965. Receipts signed by the University Treasurer. Includes information on stock dividends and loose paper reciepts from other transactions. Good Condition. Loose receipts are kept within pages as well as some delicately glued on receipts, so please turn pages delicately.; Large pale green receipt book (17" x 14"). Good Condition. (Volume 1-3: RG0008, Series 2, Volume 2)
    - Trust Funds Cash Receipts Vol. 3, January, 1965 - June, 1966; This book includes reciepts for cash payments recieved by the University from April 29, 1963 - January 17, 1965. Receipts signed by the University Treasurer. Includes information on stock dividends and loose paper reciepts from other transactions. Good Condition. Loose receipts are kept within pages as well as some delicately glued on receipts, so please turn pages delicately. (Volume 1-3: RG0008, Series 2, Volume 3)
  - Student Activity Fees, September, 1926 - August, 1928; This book contains a running list of student activity fee payments deposited into GWU accounts between September 26, 1926 and August 20, 1928. Specifies some details on specific student organizations making deposits.; Medium sized ledger book. Measures 14" x 9". Dark fabric covers with red lether corners and spine. Large tear in front cover's fabric. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Office of Student Activities
  - Student Loan Fund Record, 1937-1959 (Box 1, Folders 2-3)
    2 volumes
    - University Loan Record | The George Washington University 1937 - 1949 Book #1, August, 1937 - September, 1950; Includes a name by name record of the university's student loans disbursements, amounts owed on balances, recapitulations, and outstanding loan balances. Rcords of 3,478 loan disbursements over 13 years recorded.; Small ledger book. Measures 8.5" x 10". Good condition. Dark fabric cover with red leather corners and spine. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Student aid
    - University Loan Record | The George Washington University 1950 - 1959 Book #2, September, 1950 - October, 1959; Includes a name by name record of the university's student loans disbursements, recapitulations, and outstanding loan balances from September 8, 1950 - October 14, 1959. By 1957, records become generalized for the toal amounts recieved for specific sessions.; Small ledger book. Measures 10" x 8.5". Very Good Condition. Dark fabric cover with red leather corners and spine. Shows some signs of wear. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Notes Payable, Ledger, 26 May 1913 - 6 January 1982; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Financial records, 1912-1969; RG0008 Series 3; 22.5 Linear feet
  This series contains Treasurer's reports, microfilm, and budget information. These records cover the dates 1912-69.
  Formerly ACC#9.
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
- Financial records, 1967-1986; RG0008 Series 4; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 4, Box 1, Box 2, Box 5)
  This series contains estate files, and gift and hospital records. These records date from 1967-86.
  Formerly ACC#21
  - Closed Estate - Betts, George A., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Closed Estate - Bischoff, Anna Marie, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pending Estate - Bolkhardt, Nina K., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Closed Estate - Bose, Norma, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Closed Estate - Bouscaren, Nancy M., undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Closed Estate - Bowling, James W. - Ins Policy Gift Donor, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Closed Estate - Boyd, Ada Bentley, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Closed Estate - Brittingham, Irene C. S., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Closed Estate - Chapman, Susannah A., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Closed Estate - Cook, Bessie E., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Closed Estate - Cooper, Mary C., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Closed Estate - Cullen, Marie Stone, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Closed Estate - DeGaetano, Inge, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Closed Estate - Depew, May F., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Closed Estate - Dulin, William S. Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Estate - Dworetsky, Samuel (Working File), undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Pending Estate - Eddy, Grace M., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Closed Estate - Eggena, Emelia, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pending Estate - DelGrasso, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pending Estate - Egbart, Freda Dorothy, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gifts and Bequests - Epstein, Nathan J., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pending Estate - Erwin, Henry Parsons - Scholarship, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pending Estate - Finney, Clinton R., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pending Estate - Fischer, Arthur A., undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Closed Estate - Fogert, Gertrude C., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Closed Estate - Freeman, Walter J., undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Closed Estate - Freidman, Harold M., undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Pending Estate - Gadde Trust (George Charline), undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Closed Estate - Gill, Thomas H., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pending Estate - Gruver, Margaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Pending Estate - Grosvenor, Melville Bell, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Pending Estate - Hall, Earl R., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Closed Estate - Hughes, Sarah J., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Pending Estate - Hardman, Frederick J., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Closed Estate - Harris, Patricia Roberts, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Closed Estate - Harvey, Emma Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Closed Estate - Hood, Mary Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Loaned back to office 11/11/1995
  - Closed Estate - Hooper, Ward L., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Pending Estate - Hyman, Sadie (Mrs.), undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Pending Estate - Horgan, Dr. Edmund, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Closed Estate - Hundley, James C. [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Closed Estate - Hundley, James C. [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Closed Estate - Kaufmann, Isabelle C., undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Closed Estate - Keiper, Helen P., undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Gifts - Trustees, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - University Center Sculpture Fund (Cons. Plant), undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gifts - Women's Activities Building Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gifts - Bacon, Curtis I., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gifts - Bethlehem Steel Co., Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gifts - Dorothy C. Bettelheim Estate - Library Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gifts - George F. Bowerman Estate - Library Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gifts - Boyden, Roger T., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gifts - Cardivascular Equipment, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Former Buckingham Fund File
  - Gifts - Thomas Henry Carroll Memorial Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Gifts - Center for Behavioral Sciences, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gifts - Center for Measurement Sciences, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gifts - Aurelia B. Crosby Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - Curator's Prizes in Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gifts - Davis Memorial Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Gifts - Dermatology and Syphilology Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gifts - Henry Gratten Doyle Memorial Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gifts - Eastman Kodak Company, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Evening Star (Annual) - Maintenance Fund of Hospital, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - R. J. and F. A. Felber (Note), undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gifts - First National City Bank of New York, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - Flint Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Gifts - Ford Foundation - Hospital Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Gifts - General Electric Educational and Charitable Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    See also: Law Center File
  - Gifts - General Motors Corporation - Grant in Aid, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Gifts - George Washington Memorial Fund - Executory Trust, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Gifts - GWU Hospital - Gift Equipment Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gifts - Agnes Bruce Greig Memorial - Dept. of Psych. Educ. and REs. Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Gifts - William W. Grier Estate - Library Fund, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gifts - Sadie Mae Harris Estate, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Holland, Mary A. W., undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Gifts - Paul T. Homan Memorial Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Gifts - Hospital Administration Building Fund (Friessen, Block), undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gifts - Hospital Building Fund - Sales of Securities, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Gifts - Hospital Library Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gifts - Hospital Building Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - Hospital Building Fund - Sales of Securities, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Gifts - Household Finance Corp., undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gifts - Howard, Frank A., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gifts - Independent College Funds of America (See Also: Mass Mutual Life), undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Jaques Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Frank R. Jellef Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gifts - Johns Manville Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gifts - Ralph Kennedy Memorial Fund (GWU Building Fund), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Gifts - Law Center Fund - Blocksheets 9/59, 09/1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gifts - Law Library Building Fund, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gifts - Mrs. Agnes E. Meyer - Hospital Addition, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Gifts - Franklin J. Lundig (See Lundig Estate (closed) for Ref.), undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - Franklin J. Lundig (See Lundig Estate (closed) for Ref.), undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gifts - Post-graduate Medical Educ., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Price Waterhouse Foundation, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Stephan E. Rice Memorial, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Gifts - Roe Conference Room Fund - Medical School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Goerge B. Roth Memorial Library Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Demon Runyon Memorial Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Thomas L. Rust, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - Millbank Foundation, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Gifts - School of Medicine Building Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Estate of Shelling, Walter O., undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sullivan, Michael, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gifts - Surgery, Education, Research Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Gifts - Schoenfeld Memorial Pharmacy Loan Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gifts - Scholarship Holders' Parent's Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Gifts - School of Government, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Texaco, Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Time" Magazine Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Travelers Auxiliary, D.C Pharmacy Assn., undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Closed, Estate - Keller, Rita, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Closed, Estate - Link, J. Harold, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Closed, Estate - Lunding, Franklin J. (See Lundig Gift File for ref.), undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Pending Estate - McNelly, Ruth J., undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Closed Estate - Morse, Willis B., undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Closed Estate - Murdock, James O., undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pending Estate - Offenberg, Lillian, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pending Estate - Offenberg, Max, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pending Estate - Philips, Charles, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pending Estate - Rice, Lawrence J. M., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pending Estate - Ross, Walter G., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Closed Estate - Samuel, Birdie L., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pending Estate - Sullivan, Orpah W., undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Closed Estate - Wilson, Elizabeth Webb, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gift - Washington Home for Foundlings - Annual Report, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gift - Washington Home for Foundlings - (See Also: GWU Cancer Clinic File), undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Audit Reports - Washington Home for Foundlings, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Gift - Washington Home for Foundlings - Beatrice Sanders Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Gift - Marion M. Bond and Mary A. Wood to Warwick Memorial, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Gift - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Gift - Walter D. Pabst Estate, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Gift - Loretta Payne Memorial - Book Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Gift - Portrait Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Gift - Trustees, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Report - Pairo Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Obstetrics and Gyneacology - Education and Research Fund, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Pfizer, Charles and Co., Inc., undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Pharmacy - Lecturer's Fund and Special Equipment, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hospital: Sale Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gray and Company, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Federal Government, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Lease/Paine Webber, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AMI, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Birnbaum Study, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center Alternative Studies, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Negotiating Team, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hogan & Hartson, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hogan & Hartson, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - (HCA, Republic, et al), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Lease/Real Estate Evaluation, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Awards, 1969-1985; RG0008 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains five awards (including one plaque) for GW building architecture. This material dates from 1969-85.
  Formerly ACC#161.
- Estate records, 1929-1989; RG0008 Series 6; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains closed estates records. These materials date from 1929-89.
  Formerly ACC#170.
  - Closed Estates: A-HA, 1940-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Closed Estates: HE-RI, 1940-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Closed Estates: RI-Z, 1929-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Financial records, RG0008 Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains records of gifts and bequests of property to the university, including the old Medical School site (square 250), 1225 New York Avenue.
  Formerly ACC#197.
  - Wright gift: Chicago condo, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hawaiian gift, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 12125 N.Y. Avenue, NW, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Duncan: D.C. Little Tavern, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Duncan: Baltimore Little Taverns, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Old Medical School site: Square 250, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Square 250 land records, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Square 250 Elder agreement, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Square 250 NY Life agreement, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Scrapbooks, 1953-1967; RG0008 Series 8; 1 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains four scrapbooks with newspaper clippings of the Foggy Bottom Urban Renewal Project. These materials date from 1953-67.
  Formerly ACC#214; clippings loose within scrapbooks ad should be re-housed.
  - Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Articles concerning urban renewal projects within the vicinity of the university and the related controversy
  - Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Articles on urban renewal projects and the related controversy; plans for medical center construction
  - Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Articles on university's urban renewal projects; slum clearing; D.C.'s proposed cultural center
  - Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Articles on urban renewal projects relating to GW as well as other DC schools; Columbia Plaza project; special section for hospital clippings
- Office files, 1982-1985; RG0008 Series 9; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains documents related to the revenue notes dated 1985, 2100 Pennsylvania Avenue, and 1982 revenue bonds. These materials date from 1982-85.
  Formerly ACC#315.
- Office files, RG0008 Series 10; 9 Linear feet
  This series contains records related to Loudoun Campus, finance committee, construction contract, progress reports, and plans/drawings for construction.
  Formerly ACC#316.
- Financial records, 1986-1989; RG0008 Series 11; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains records related to GW investments and divestitures in South Africa. These records date from 1986-89.
  Formerly ACC#481
- Financial records, 1982-1990; RG0008 Series 12; 13.5 Linear feet
  This series contains records related to the Burns Clinic expansion, Square 250 leases/construction, 1925 F Street, 2000 Penn. Avenue taxes, and other real estate holdings. These records cover the dates 1982-90.
  Formerly ACC#566.
  - Silvan Bonge, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Square 250: Elder Lease, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Square 250: Approved New York Life Lease, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Plot of Subdivision, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Square 250: Walker and Dunlop, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Square 250: Chase, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Square 250: New York Life, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Square 250: Sub-Tenants, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Health Policy Forum: 2011 Eye Street NW, Suite 200, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - David H Levesque: Crystal City Center, Cleaning Services, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2021 K Street NW, Suite 710: HIA, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Red Cross: Loudoun County, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Dulles Board, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Red Cross Building: 22nd and Eye Street Property, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1730 K Street NW, Suite 702 North, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2520 L Street NW, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    C-56311-T03243
  - 10620 Georgia Ave, Silver Spring: Infant Lab, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Maryland
  - Association of University Related Research Parks, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Medical Center Expansion: Square 75, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Rental Analysis